Guide to the Cornell University International Agriculture records, 1952-1980.
Cornell University International Agriculture records
- Series XV. Alphabetical File Files
  - National Dairy Research Institute, India, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation - Seed Program, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Nebraska, University of, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina State University, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - O, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Ohio State University - International Affairs, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Oregon State University - Weed Control Project USAID, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Organization of American States, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Organization of Tropical Studies(OTS), 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Orientation Program, 1968-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Educational Service, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Overseas Employment Opportunities, 1964-1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - P, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Peace Corps - Future Agriculture Research Manpower(F.A.R.M.) Program, 1972-1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Personnel, 1970-1976 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Philippine, Modern Project (Frank Golay), 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Phills, Dr. Bobby R., 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Plantas Alimenticias Andinas, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Plant Protection Center - Taiwan, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Policies for Science and Technology in Developing Nations, Program(PPSTDN) of Cornell University, 1969-1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Policies for Science and Technology in Developing Nations, Program - PPSTDN - Summer Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Professors-at-Large, A.D. White(J.George Harrar), 1970-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Professors-at-Large - J.George Harrar, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Professors-at-Large - J.George Harrar, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Professors-at-Large - J.George Harrar's 1976 Visit, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Program Direction Committee - International Agriculture, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Progress Reports - College of Agriculture and Life Science(CALS) International Development - K.L. Turk and C.E. Palm, 1961-1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Publications Committee, 1969-1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Perdue Fellows in Latin America Program, 1965-1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Q, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - R, 1967-1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1967-1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Ecuador, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Fellows at Cornell University, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Fellowship Officer, 1961-1976 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Mexico, 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Newsletters, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - New York, 1968-1977 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Rotary, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - S, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Southeast Asian Regional Center for Graduate Study and Research in Agriculture(SEARCA), 1968-1972 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - South Pacific Commission, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Sponsored Programs (Academic Funding), 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - T, 1970-1976 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Texas A and M, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - United Nations Development Program, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization(UNESCO), 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - United States Department of Agriculture(USDA), 1964-1975 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - United States International University, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Veterinary College, Cornell University, 1971-1975 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - W, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1966-1974 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - World Bank, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - World Studies Data Bank, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - X,Y,Z, 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 36)